Come on, come on, come on!
Hey, hey, hey!
Copy that, unit 12.
They're in the van!
Get these people out of here.
-Clear!
-Oh my God! He's got a gun.
Get down, get down! Get down!
Come on. Down. Down, down, down, down!
Smoke!
Go!
Behind you! Bag!
Hurry up!
Coming up on your six!
On your six!
Overwhelm. Go!
Go.
Move!
Motherfucker!
That's a big fucking gun!
-Fall back.
-What the fuck?!
Jesus fucking Christ!
Fuck you!
Officer down!
Not today.
Brinkley, go, go!
Fall back!
-'Trane, come on!
-Come on!
Let's go!
Shit!
I got you. I'll clear a path.
Fuck you, bitch!
Watch out!
Nigga, what the--
You can bench me later!
For now, I'm covering you.
Let’s get this motherfucker!
Wait! Riley! Riley!
Riley!
-Shit.
-Fuck!
Okay, listen.
When I give you the order, you cover me.
I'm going up one car over.
Okay?
-Alright, give it to him, give it to him.
-Move!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Brinkley!
Fall back!
Hey, hey, hey! What's wrong?
Officer down!
Brinkley, hey, Brinkley!
Look at me, Brinkley!
You're gonna fight. You're gonna live.
You fight, and you'll live.
Shit!
Come on, nigga!
Stro.
Go.
Fuck!
This is the police!
Drop your weapons
and surrender immediately!
You are surrounded!
Where the fuck is he?
Freeze, motherfucker.
Drop it.
Backup transpo.
Gold Honda Accord,
corner of Thayer and Verona.
Charlie says, "You're welcome."
Looks like I got the wrong guy.
Sorry to have disturbed you, sir.
I tossed a duffel bag
in the alley dumpster around the corner.
Find it and burn it.
You have a nice day.
You guys got everything?
I need to talk to him.
Two minutes.
Yep.
I thought your crew was smarter than this.
You're shooting cops in broad daylight.
That's the death penalty, nigga.
And even if your boy Choi, if he lives,
both y'all about to get gassed up,
and that's if y'all even make it to trial,
'cause you know that jail
is a dangerous motherfucking place
for some cop killers.
You know that, right?
Mm-mm.
I'll tell you what.
Maybe I can figure out a way
to get you into ISO
long enough to see trial.
I can do you that solid.
If you tell me…
where Nightmare is.
Lawyer, motherfucker.
Yeah, I was hoping you'd say that.
Tell me where Nightmare is.
Tell me where Nightmare is, Stro.
Come on!
Tell me where Nightmare is!
I know this shit hurts, Stro!
-Come on, nigga, tell me where he is!
-Whoa! Back up! You can't be doing that!
-Fine!
-Let's go!
You take real good care of this man.
We got plans for him.
Fuck you, nigga!
Where the fuck you at, man?
It's a goddamn bloodbath.
I got good police on the way
to the morgue.
Got even more headed to the ER,
where I got a bunch of innocent civilians
hit in the crossfire,
and I got the chief
crawling so far up my ass,
I chipped a tooth on his cuff links.
What I don't got is a fucking clue
of what happened here,
but I know you do because you told Yvette
to bring backup to this exact location.
And Vig, who is dead,
called me to tell me the same damn thing!
So talk!
I got a tip about Coltrane Wilder.
-We showed up. They started shooting.
-You saw Wilder?
-He was wearing a mask.
-Then you didn't see him!
I'm sick of this shit, Isaiah!
Who gave you the tip?
I can't say.
You can't?
Ain't this a bitch?
After all the shit I done
protecting your ass,
you're gonna do me like this.
You see all that blood on the ground?
All that blood is about to turn to shit.
Bionic type shit
because it don't roll downhill.
It runs uphill like a goddamn Kenyan,
and I'm gonna be up to my neck in it
if I don't have answers!
I'm sorry, Captain.
I--
You think he's gonna listen to me?
All right.
I'm gonna make this
real simple for you, Isaiah.
Either give me answers…
or give me your gun and badge.
All right.
If that's how you're gonna play it,
get your ass back to RHD for questioning.
IA's gonna wanna speak with you.
You're flying solo now, Isaiah.
Bon fucking voyage.
A citywide manhunt
for two cop killers is underway…
I'm telling you,
my Galil was spitting heat!
Dropping bombs, nigga!
Sound like we brought World War 3
to the motherfucking streets of LA!
Yo, this shit all in my feed.
-Hey, yo. You like OJ and shit.
-Nigga, OJ only got two bodies.
I killed more police
than cholesterol, nigga.
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam!
Hey, yo, what the fuck's funny, nigga?
-Show some respect.
-Respect?
You think this Morgan Freeman-looking
motherfucker killed the police?
This janitor-looking nigga
look like he can't take out the trash.
You done fucked up now.
What, I'm supposed to be scared
of this puff of smoke in the onesie?
Think I'm too old to fuck you up?
I think you're too old
to fuck, period, OG.
You probably can't--
-Whoa!
-Jesus.
Looks like I got me some new threads.
Thought I said I needed a clean car
and someone to check on my house too!
Here.
Go get 50 Melo burgers
and every kind of shake they got.
Fucking niggas up make me hungry!
Isaiah?
Hey, uh…
Hey, you're-- you're home early.
Yeah, um…
I don't know. I don't know
how to tell you this, but, um…
My father, he was involved in a massive
shootout with the police this morning.
Amos? What…
Uh, just… look at this shit.
There are multiple, multiple casualties…
Oh, sh…
He shot Brinkley right in front of me.
Oh my God. Is… is Brinkley…?
No, he's in the hospital, but I can't go
because I gotta get Amos first.
If they get to him,
you know what they'll do.
Shoot first, ask questions never.
Okay, but is that really
why you wanna find him?
To save him?
I mean, I need to bring him in
for a whole lot of things.
Top of that list is
because he is the only one
who can identify the guy
who brought him into this shit.
It's the same guy that
I've been hunting this whole time.
The same guy who killed Manny.
Coltrane Wilder?
You think I wouldn't figure that out
after you raided Ebony's house?
Yes, yes. Coltrane Wilder,
who knew I was close to getting his ass,
so he brought my father
into his latest crime to fuck me up.
No, fuck that. I'm…
I'm taking Noah to my father's house,
where things will be safe
until this all settles down.
Okay, yeah, that's good.
It's not safe until I find him.
I'm gonna call you later.
-I'm gonna figure it out.
-Sh…
Sure you'll figure it out.
I can't believe this. I can't believe…
Goddamn it, Coltrane.
It's all over the news.
-Things went a little left.
-A little?
I keep asking you,
and you keep giving me the same line.
"Everything's under control."
But that's not what I saw on the TV.
-Ebony…
-No, Coltrane, I'm done asking.
Now I'm telling you. It's time to go.
I'm getting on a jet with Charlie tonight
at midnight. You need to be on it too.
I'll be there.
There's one thing I need.
Put your sister on the phone.
Coltrane.
Please, Ebony.
I'll be on the plane. I just…
I need to talk to Charlie first.
He wants to talk to you.
Hey.
We got this.
-What the fuck happened?
-It doesn't matter.
What matters is what happens now.
And right now I need to find the wheelman
and put him down.
I can't have a loose end
walking around the streets.
He's a cop killer.
Chances are they'll shoot him on sight.
Let the LAPD do your job for you.
Charlie, I can't stake
my future on chance.
I gotta know for sure
he's never gonna talk.
Give me a name. I'll put my people on it.
Help me help you, Coltrane.
Amos Stiles.
The cop's daddy?
You took what was already
a very high-risk job,
taking down a man
that could jeopardize both our futures,
and you decided
this was a good two-for-one opportunity?
It was worth the risk.
Nightmare's prints are
on the murder weapon.
When they find that,
Stiles' case against us crumbles,
along with his credibility
in the department.
He'll be completely compromised.
And we won't have to worry about Stiles.
It's a good fucking plan.
What part of the plan
was getting in a shootout in Century City?
Unforeseen circumstances.
Listen, we reacted as best as we could.
And now I got word that Stro and Choi
are in the hospital.
And the guy you wanna take the fall
is in the wind.
You don't think I fucking know that?
I saw them both go down. I tried to…
I couldn't get to them.
That's why I need to finish this shit.
I need to carry out the plan.
No, the only plan you should have is being
at that OB-GYN appointment with Ebony
to solidify your alibi, and then
be on that jet tonight, all right?
I'll handle Nightmare.
-I'm already looking for Nightmare.
-Look, you have done enough, all right?
You need to act like citizen Wilder
while I handle this shit.
Focus on being there for my sister.
We good?
We good.
Stiles, it's Cerullo.
Brinkley is still alive, but critical.
Doctors are operating on him now.
And I'll keep you posted
if I hear anything else.
Where's Nightmare?
Oh, shit. This nigga done lost his daddy.
Yeah, I'm not the one,
not today, not ever.
-Now move aside, man.
-Whoa!
Now I said your daddy ain't here,
so unless you got a warrant,
you're gonna have to take my word
on that shit.
I don't need no warrant.
Hear that loud rap music?
You know that's
the probable cause theme song, right?
Whoa.
You thought I'd pull a piece on you,
serve up some probable cause? Nah.
We some Blacktivist niggas around here,
documenting police brutality
for these here streets.
Got the world watching.
Now, Mr. Police Officer,
what you think about that?
We live, baby.
Hey, Mama.
Hi.
How's our baby?
I didn't think you were gonna make it.
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Glad you could be here.
We were just about
to begin the ultrasound. Ready?
Yeah.
Take them heels off
Before you jump up in this drop, bitch
She ask how much cost syrup in my cup
That's a lot, bitch
Ain't no more purple
So I'm drinkin' yellow snot, bitch
Got some choppers
Got a plug, then I got rich
Cashed out on three Lamborghinis
Just to pop shit
I brought the millions to the circle
Nigga, mob shit
I pray to God my son don't get cursed
For some shit I did
I hit 'em in the chest
And tell 'em that the world his
I put it all on the line
'Cause I'm a gambler, nigga
Just bought my brother
A motherfuckin' Phantom, lil' nigga
I kidnapped this bitch
She let her phone stay dead for 3 days
I just poured a eight
Of Wock' Wock' in a pitcher of Kool-Aid
My barber get a hundo
Every time I get a new fade
Blue Aventador
Blue diamonds at the Blue Flame…
Fuck!
I, uh… I have to take this.
I'll be right back.
I could never, ever chase a bitch…
I'm gonna find him,
and then I'm gonna take you down.
Not if I find him first.
Oh, wow.
So everything looks okay?
Well, it's early, but all indicators point
to a healthy full-term pregnancy.
Look. All the tests are coming in
with flying colors.
Here are your screening results.
What's this? It-- It says,
"Decision to terminate prior pregnancy."
What decision?
I thought we had to do it.
Well, there was a placental abruption,
which posed a significant risk
to your life, but it was a choice.
I… I told you this
as you were coming out of the anesthesia,
but perhaps
things are a little foggy for you.
Because you were unconscious,
and your husband wasn't present,
your sister made the decision
to terminate the pregnancy.
My sister?
She didn't tell you?
Forgive me. I have to leave.
Oh, it's okay. Um, we were just finishing.
Thank you.
Coltrane. I--
Ebony.
Just be on that plane tonight.
I will.
We have just received the identity
of one of the injured police officers.
Detective Jamel Brinkley
was shot at the scene
and is currently in critical condition
at Cedars-Sinai…
I… I don't understand.
Detective Brinkley was just at our house
for Thanksgiving with Grandpa.
There's no way Grandpa would have
done that, shoot police.
Noah, honey, maybe you don't know
Amos as well as you think.
I know him better than you.
I've been going over his house for weeks.
-What?
-You don't watch him closely enough.
You wouldn't let me see my own grandpa,
so I have to sneak over.
And I know he wouldn't do
what they're saying.
Okay, Noah, this is nothing new for Amos.
Your other grandfather has been involved
in gangs and crime his whole life, son.
He's… He's changed. He's not like that.
Amos' character
can't be learned in just a few weeks.
You need to look at a man's whole life
to know who he is.
-Daddy.
-It is time he knew the truth about Amos.
Now is not the time.
Candy. Candy.
The boy's ready.
You know Amos
was involved in the life, right?
But he wasn't just another banger.
No, what you have to understand
is that he got that name Nightmare
for a reason.
He was a violent man who brought
his own son Josiah into the gang.
He was even proud of the fact
that he got the nickname Little Nightmare,
proud that Josiah was becoming violent
just like his daddy.
But that life only ends in two ways,
and Amos knew that.
What ways?
Dead or in jail.
Unfortunately for Josiah,
it was the former.
Nightmare took him on a robbery,
and while he was inside the house,
Josiah was shot dead
by a rival gang in the car.
Nightmare came out shooting,
but it was too late.
Ended up fulfilling
the other fate of a banger.
That's what put him in jail.
That's how his son got killed.
That's the kind of man Amos is.
Someone who cared more about gang life
than he did his own family.
Look, sweetie,
that's why your father tries so hard
to be different than his father.
-"He tries." Wha-- Please.
-Mom, not helping.
She's right. He… He's not different.
-He's just like him.
-Noah.
He care more about all his cop shit
than his own family. They're the same.
Am I gonna be like him?
Is every man in this family fucked up
just in a different way?
-Language!
-Noah, listen to me.
Amos is his own man.
Your father is his own man.
We all make choices
about what kind of man we're gonna be.
So it's up to you, Noah.
You get to decide
what kind of man you're gonna be.
Why you at my spot?
-Peace offering.
-Fuck your peace offering. I'm on duty.
You know a sixer is like a fucking
amuse-bouche to your Samoan ass. Come on.
What the fuck you want, Stiles?
You're making me lose my appetite,
and that's hard to do.
-I know I fucked up.
-Fucked up big time.
-You don't owe me anything.
-Damn right.
But you know about that shit
at Century City.
I am this close to catching
one of the shooters and I need your help.
Hey, he's an old OG.
-He'll try to bust out the country.
-How you know that?
That's what I would do
if I was in the kind of shit he's in.
Come on, Ika.
You know players in the trafficking game
who fuck with the bangers. I need names.
You need to go home.
I heard your ass was suspended,
and this here's my celebration dinner.
Ika.
The shooter is my father.
It's Nightmare.
That's fucked up, Stiles.
-That's real fucked up.
-Yeah.
I appreciate you.
If anybody else comes to you,
let's just keep this to yourself.
Hey.
He may be your pop,
but he's a cop killer.
He needs to get got.
Anybody come and ask for names,
they gonna have 'em.
Now get the fuck out of my face.
Hey.
You go.
That stays.
Hey, did something happen to Isaiah?
Nothing yet, I hope.
But I wanna keep it that way,
so I need to know where he is.
I saw him at the house a few hours ago,
but I haven't heard from him since.
Shouldn't you be with him
trying to find the shooters?
Stiles has been suspended, Candace.
What--? What do you mean suspended?
Sounds like he didn't tell you,
which shocks nobody.
Stiles was suspended and sent back to RHD
for questioning, but he never showed.
Now, whatever he's doing out there
is off book and unsanctioned.
It's only going
to make it worse for him and you.
Now, if you hear from him again,
you need to give me a call, okay?
I gotta go. Bye.
Fuck.
Candace doesn't know anything.
I'm scrubbing through local CCTV footage.
Uh, you do that Gen Z millennial shit
and check social media.
Yeah. On it, Captain.
I don't fucking believe it.
You know who that is?
That's Amos Stiles.
No, that's a fucking "Nightmare."
Let's go. You drive.
Can't bring that in here, old timer.
This goes where I go.
Tell Earl Nightmare's at the door.
Hype me up, hype me up
Hype me up
I hype me up…
Just because you're young
don't mean you gotta be dumb.
Make the call. Live another day.
Oh, man.
-Whatever happened to Big Head Bobby?
-He's been dead.
Bitch shot his ass.
Wasn't the bullet that killed him.
Nigga's brain just got too much oxygen.
Those were different times, man.
We was wild in the streets.
Oh, goddamn right!
But you-- you--
you was always a slick motherfucker.
Ain't no surprise you built all this
while I was on the inside.
Lot of blood, sweat, and tears
in this place.
Not your blood, I bet.
Shit, man, you know me.
Sometimes the old ways are the best way.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So tell me.
What you come around here for
after all this time?
I need to get south.
I heard you got that
real quiet-type import-export service
out of Mexico that I require.
You heard right.
But I ain't no border coyote
working for pesos and shit.
What I offer is top shelf. So you want
that platinum package? I got that.
But it's gonna cost you,
history or no history.
I'm a business nigga now.
Maybach and G-Wagon trucks…
And I'm a motivated nigga.
A lot of cash and very little time.
Say no more.
You've come to the right place.
I slip you down to Guadalajara,
get you a new ID.
Chill you out in a fresh hacienda
for a couple of weeks.
Push you down south to a country
where the dollar can definitely holla
and the long arm of Johnny law
will never reach your old ass.
All you gotta do
is talk to my guy later on tonight.
Till then, enjoy the amenities.
Stomp a lil' pussy ho
With some shell toes
Yeah Glo! Slappin' rap bitches…
Here you go, baby.
What the fuck are you doing here?
No one has proof
you're involved in this shit,
but if they see you here,
that's a big red flag.
We both want the same thing.
Nightmare dead.
But it's us versus the entire LAPD,
so we need to work together on this.
That wasn't the plan.
Stiles changed the plans.
So you find Nightmare,
I kill him,
and you bag a body and a promotion.
Shit!
Let's go out the back. I'll head them off.
We could try Stiles' house.
Maybe look around the back.
Captain, Cruz. I saw the car pull up.
Harper, what are you doing here?
Earlier today, I saw something
that didn't sit right with me.
Stiles had a shot at one of the suspects
and didn't take it.
He left the scene
before I could talk to him.
And he wasn't at his house, so I looked up
the residence of his next of kin.
Looked around back,
but there's nobody here.
It appears one of the shooters
is Stiles' father,
Amos Stiles, aka, Nightmare.
-Could be why he didn't take the shot.
-Shit.
Guess that makes sense with what I saw.
Right now we need to focus
on finding Nightmare, not Stiles.
Then I want in.
Those men killed my partner.
I wanna be there when we take him down.
Fair enough, but you and me are gonna have
a sit-down when we get back.
You should have called it in.
You shouldn't be out here without backup.
Saddle up. You're riding shotgun.
No, I'll ride in the back. He's the boss.
So, if you were an old gangster
on the run, what would you do?
I'd try to get to Mexico
through one of my old contacts.
Call Ika Matangi in Gang Unit.
He knows the players.
Hey, Matangi. Yeah, it's Cruz. I--
How'd you know why I was calling?
Yeah, thanks.
Stiles just got this name off of him.
Just can't stop digging.
Earl Hayes.
He used to run with Amos back in the day.
Mm, I know exactly where to find him.
Tanya, does Lotta still work at that club?
Lotta, where your ass going?
I'm taking my smoke break.
Wait, wait, wait. Over there.
Fast money, fast whips, it's the life
I had to go and get it…
-I gotta pat you down, player.
-Don't touch me. No need.
-I'm a cop.
-Okay, cop, let me see your cop badge.
-I must have left it in the car.
-Ah.
No badge, no gun.
Shh, be quiet, lеt me pop off
Leave thе club sloppy drunk
Come home and get my rocks off
Heard "Bitch from Da Souf"
He tryna see me knock his socks off
Told them bitches, "Meet me at the top"
Think they got lost
I'm on go like Grizz
She thought I would kiss her ass…
You must be a really good cop
to find me here.
I'd be proud if you weren't the last
motherfucker I wanted to see today.
Come on.
Let's have a sit.
But shit is not a joke
Say she got a problem
Imaginary smoke
Bitches said it's up
Then put it on the floor
I done done it all
Feel like Shawty Lo
Laughin' to the bank
But shit is not a joke…
Yeah, I always knew you wasn't shit,
but never pegged you to be a sucker.
Coltrane used you to get to me.
See?
It's always been your fucking problem,
going around
thinking everything's about you.
Oh, you must be forgetting shit
in your old age.
Who's been supporting
your broke convict ass all these years?
That's been me.
I pay your rent, nigga. I pay your bills.
$327,556 dollars. That's how much I spent
trying to keep you off these streets.
Now I see you out there
in broad daylight shooting cops?
Cut me off,
said I was nothing but a criminal,
so I went out and did some criminal shit.
Now I gotta bring you in to answer
for that too, or else I'm fucked.
Suddenly, me being a step ahead,
it looks different.
Looks like I'm part of this shit.
Is that what you want?
Laughin' to the bank
But shit is not a joke…
You hate me that much?
If not, you need to ID Coltrane.
I done done it all, feel like Shawty Lo
Laughin' to the bank…
You snatched Josiah's chain from my neck
because you know
that's the most important shit I own.
See, Josiah knew.
He knew a real man don't snitch on nobody.
A real man protects his family.
That's something you never understood.
Josiah found it out the hard way.
I got these bitches mad again…
Cops is out front,
so I hate to break up
this touching family reunion, Nightmare,
but you, out the back.
I'll make him eat me through the pants
Stay on her mind
She keep stalkin' like a spy…
-Amos.
-Whoa.
I can't have you and your pop
shooting it out in the parking lot, so…
if you could sit tight for a spell.
I'm all on your nigga face
I might twerk a lil' bit
This your nigga
But he fuckin' with the jit
She like, "Drop the lo'"
But I am not tryna hit…
Or you can head on out the front door.
But you're a cop without a badge.
Something tells me
you don't play well with your friends.
Beefin' 'bout some balls
Hell nah, let's just compare bankrolls
Got him on his knees
Ain't talkin' 'bout ring
He ain't propose
A-ha, a-ha
Bitch, I took your ho
You ain't like that
Said he was yours
Tryna see why yeen got him back
Break his pockets, give me money
Make him drop racks
Should've never gave it up so fast
Why you let him smack?
Tonight, we continue our coverage
of the deadly shooting in Century City,
where authorities are piecing together
what led to the chaos…
Candy. Here, sweetie.
Thank you, thank you.
What do you think will happen
if Isaiah were to catch up with Amos?
You don't think
he'd shoot his own son, do you?
God only knows what a Stiles man would do.
I just wish that he would call,
so I just would know he's safe.
Okay. All right.
-Sit.
-Mom.
Please have a seat.
Please.
Do you hear yourself right now?
You are a grown-ass woman acting like
a schoolgirl waiting for some boy to call.
No, no, let me tell you something.
While you are sitting here
thinking and stressing over Isaiah,
he is out there running the streets
doing God knows what,
but you know
the one thing he is not doing?
'Cause I can tell you.
He is not thinking about you.
Now what you need to be thinking about
is a good divorce attorney.
-Mom.
-Mm.
Whatever happened
to that nice Jacobson boy?
Mom, please don't bring up Malik.
Malik. Yes.
Yeah. I like Malik. You could trust Malik.
Clock's ticking.
When I said wheels up at midnight,
I meant it.
You hear me?
He'll be here.
About time. I've been waiting on you.
I got the whip out. You got that money?
Whoa, whoa. Why the rush, man?
Everybody on the block
already at Sheri's spot.
And you know she got
hoes for days over there, homie.
And I ain't trying to be late. I'm on
"early bird catch the worm" type shit.
You ain't catching nothing
with that inchworm you got.
Nigga, I'm the one catching a worm.
It's a metaphor, motherfucker.
Fuck your worm, nigga. What car you get?
Golden Tercel. Clean plates.
Here's your key, OG.
Appreciate it, homie.
Five Gs. Not bad for a bit of driving.
Not bad if I'm a dumb motherfucker.
See, nigga, I done watch you hand out
cash all day like you Oprah or some shit.
Made me wonder how much money you got.
I mean, you should be
sharing the wealth, right?
So you can keep this weak-ass half a band.
I don't need that shit.
What I need, nigga, is half of what's
in that there suitcase. I mean…
You feel me?
So that's how it is?
Yeah, nigga, that's how it is.
I mean, shit.
I could have taken the whole thing.
Lucky I'm feeling generous.
See, this is the problem
with you young motherfuckers.
Got no respect for nothing.
Running around with your pants
around your ankles, posting videos.
A bunch of Instaniggas,
hoeing yourself out for likes.
You're too focused on the wrong shit.
See? Like right now,
you think, 'cause my piece is tucked
around my back, and yours is in the front,
that you got the jump
on an old motherfucker.
But see?
You focused on the wrong shit again.
See how many likes you get
with that shit, nigga.
Isaiah, are you okay?
I had him. Candace, I fucking-- I had him.
But he got away.
He's probably halfway to Mexico by now.
So what does that mean?
It means you can take Noah home.
It's safe.
No. No, no, no,
what does that mean for you?
Means I probably need a lawyer.
A lawyer. Jesus, Isaiah.
I don't know. I'll tell you more
when I get to the house.
I did what I had to do.
Okay.
We'll meet you there.
I'm meeting Isaiah at the house now.
Stiles is headed home.
Flip a bitch.
What the fuck?
Hey, yo, B-Roll, you gotta come through
and bring some of that za--
Where is he?
-He's here. He's fucking dead.
-Old man. Nightmare, motherfucker.
I don't know.
Try harder.
Shit, man, I got him a clean ride,
a golden Tercel, and it wasn't out front,
and I figured the nigga left, all right?
Tell me where he went or you about to have
a sleepover with that motherfucker.
-You hear me?
-Don't know. On the dead homies, I swear.
The chain.
What if half the things ever said
Turned out to be a lie
How will you know the truth?
If you were given all the answers
And you stopped to wonder why
But how will you know the truth?
Everybody's got a right to love
Everybody's got a right to lie
But the choice you make
It ain't no piece of cake
It ain't no motherfucking piece of pie
What If time's only reason
Was to give us all somethin' to fear?
You gotta turn yourself in.
My dad's in a lot of trouble,
but you can help him.
All you have to do is wait here.
He'll be home any minute.
I can't do that, little man.
I'm not going back in.
Not for Isaiah, not for you.
Then do it for yourself.
You've done so much bad shit,
you probably think
it's too late to change, but it's not.
As long as you're alive,
you can still make choices.
You can't change anything you've done.
You can't bring Josiah back,
but you can still save your other son.
There's your dad.
He can't find you in here with me.
Wait.
Wait. What are you doing?
Sit tight there.
I'll handle your dad.
Don't come out until we're gone.
Wait, for… for what?
Good speech, son.
I can see what kind of man
you're gonna be.
Wa… Wait, Grandpa.
Motherf--
There's people tryna kill me
Other than me
My heart is like a drum
Rrdd-umpum-pumpum-pum
I can't say what I want
My conscience weighs a ton
There's nowhere I can run
I thought it would be fun
If I grabbed everyone
Inside the room and--
Decided they're all done
And do them somethin' foul
Like burn them to the ground
I don't feel safe and sound
My ego makes me trip
And kicks me while I'm down
When no one is around
I can't throw in the towel
Gunshots played over nurseries
I lost real guys in a robbery
Fast food
Cigarettes in my arteries
Rapper dead
Making bank off the catalogue
Real beef
Turn that into a sing-along
My brother laid out mixin' wrong pills
Irony is that he got 'em from a MD
Somehow you would've thought
That would've stopped me
Pop one, pop two, I'ma pop star
Who's tryna see a real G-O-D?
You can see it in my face, I'ma hard R
You will never get my real P-O-V
My thoughts get dark when it's just me
This world's fucked up, is it just me?
Just me and my withering psyche
There's people tryna kill me
Other than me